{"data":[{"question":"The public issue is not worth ___.","a":"discuss","b":"discussing","c":"discussed","d":"being discussed","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be worth verb_ing: used to say that something is interesting, useful","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"All the children enjoy ___ by the beach with their parents.","a":"play","b":"to play","c":"playing","d":"to be playing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Enjoy doing something.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The doctor told the fat man ___ less and ___ more.","a":"eat, exercise","b":"to eat, exercise","c":"eat, to exercise","d":"eating, exercising","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tell sbd to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Let me ___ if you has decided ___it.","a":"to know, do","b":"to know, to do","c":"know, do","d":"know, to do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Let somebody do something\n- Decide to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"In class you should listen to your teacher ___ English!","a":"speak","b":"to speak","c":"spoke","d":"speaks","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Listen to sbd do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"James was walking in a park when he heard his name ___.","a":"to be called","b":"to call","c":"calling","d":"called","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Hear\/ Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Passive voice: - Find\/ see\/ watch...+ PP ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Whatever she said, Claire couldn't make herself ___.","a":"to understand","b":"understand","c":"understood","d":"understanding","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Make someone understood","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"I prefer _________ by others rather than ___.","a":"be driven, to drive","b":"being driven, driving","c":"to drive, driving","d":"driving, driving","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Prefer + To Verb + rather than + Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you mean by saying that? \"I meant no harm. I only ___.\"","a":"want to help","b":"mean helping","c":"want helping","d":"meant to help","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Verb in past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The director needs to confirm ___.","a":"when start","b":"to start","c":"When starting","d":"when to start","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Some verbs: ask, decide, explain, forget, know, show, tell, understand, can be followed by a question word such as where\/ how\/ what\/ who\/ when or whether + To Verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}